An unidentified body has been found
at 71-1 Sunghan-dong, Jongno-gu.
I repeat, unidentified body found.
Officers needed.
Unit One is en route.
This number is not available.
Please check the number again…
I don't see it.
Where's your ticket to Hawaii?
Right here. I put it here myself.
Hold on.
This number is not…
Goddamn it!
CHOI HYE-JEONG
What?
I just got a call
from Son Myeong-o's aunt.
He died, apparently.
His body was found last night.
You sure have a large social circle.
You keep in touch with his aunt?
Well, I keep in touch with you too.
Hey.
What you said was true, you know.
Friendship alone can't keep us going.
You don't even know
what I have up my sleeve.
Yeon-jin.
You're so fucked!
Thanks for letting me know.
I seem to have just lost two friends.
You really want me to sell the motel?
But the business is going well.
Sell it.
I don't care if it's dirt cheap,
just sell it.
Find a real estate agent tomorrow
and call me.
Oh, where have you been?
Did you have lunch?
Business was good last night, eh?
We had some instant noodles.
Why do you guys only eat instant noodles?
Have some jjigae instead. Yeah.
Here.
Boss, you're the best.
Still working for Yeon-jin?
Yes, I make some extra cash from it.
All right. Then have a good one.
Don't forget. No minors.
Yes, sir. Drive safe.
Sure.
How often do you drink?
What are you talking about?
I've never had a drop of alcohol
in my entire life.
Just ask my daughter.
My daughter's a teacher. A teacher!
You were diagnosed
with alcohol dependency six years ago.
Are you saying you haven't
had a drink since then?
Um, about that…
Right, just one glass.
The glass was only half full.
And I didn't even drink it all at once.
How much do you drink
once you start drinking?
How many bottles?
I said I don't drink!
How dare you, you quack!
I see why you brought me here.
You fucking bitch!
You two are ganging up on me, aren't you?
-Why did you start the fire?
-What fire?
It was just a small burn on the floor!
I was just trying
to talk some sense into her.
You know, there's a fire extinguisher
in every house these days.
We put out the fire quickly. Quickly.
What a convenient world we live in!
I think we're done here. You may leave.
I can leave?
Really?
CONSENT FORM FOR ADMISSION
PATIENT: JEONG MI-HEE
FAMILY RELATION CERTIFICATE
The documents are now confirmed.
This way.
Let go!
You bastards! Let go!
Dong-eun! These people are taking me away!
Say something. Come on!
I'm the only one
who can do this to you, Mom.
Because I am
your only blood.
I won't be able to visit often.
You bitch!
How could you? I'm your mother.
You fucking snake!
Hey! Let go, you assholes!
I'll go with this for the flooring.
As for the wallpaper, let's see…
What's going on between you and Ms. Moon?
You startled me. Hello.
I didn't sneak up on you.
Are you done picking?
No, not yet.
I'm debating whether I should go
with mid-century modern white
or Bauhaus gray.
Oh, I'm so torn.
What a nice way to treat a rental home.
Get him whichever one's more expensive.
Sure, okay!
Did your new tenant already vacate?
No, the house caught fire.
Oh, I heard about the fire yesterday.
That was yours?
Oh no, how did that happen?
Are they paying for the damages?
No, none of that. I didn't say anything.
The tenant who lives there saved my life.
What? Really?
Is that her?
Was your father involved in tax evasion
through your art exhibitions?
Some say he used his followers' names
to buy paintings to evade gift tax.
Do you regret doing drugs?
Ms. Lee, give us a comment!
Drink up. Tomatoes are good for detox.
What happened to that Yeon-jin bitch?
Is that the first thing
you're going to say to your mom?
I lost weight from being so anxious.
Can't you see?
When do I have to show up at the station?
They'll let you know some time next week.
If you cooperate with the investigation,
it will help reduce your sentence,
so it's better if you show up.
Ugh, so annoying! Shit!
Have you looked for my phone?
That old thing? It was in your old room.
Why do you need it?
It contains a precious memory.
Some bitch's face.
Let's go there.
-Where?
-Their food was good.
You mean there? Sure, okay.
Oh, I'm so hungry.
Oh, shoot!
You're wearing matching clothes!
Poor you, Yeon-jin.
You must be so embarrassed.
Wow, this means
you two are practically besties.
A moment worth capturing.
Shut up, both of you.
Hey. You!
Take it off.
-What?
-Are you deaf like your mom?
Strip and stop freaking
talking back to me!
She's shit-scared.
I'm sorry, Yeon-jin.
These aren't real.
They are fake.
-She said fake!
-I'm so sorry.
Hey, she bolted!
Yeon-jin is so pissed.
I'm going to kill that bitch.
Look at how pissed she is!
Fuck, put that away!
MY DAUGHTER WAS A VICTIM
OF SCHOOL VIOLENCE
BULLIED HER BY BURNING HER
WITH CURLING IRON AND CIGARETTES
"A" WORKS AT A BROADCASTING STATION
AS A WEATHER FORECASTER
There was this sentence
in the online posting.
"My daughter had left home
to go to an academy, but fell
from a derelict building and died."
Do you think it's true?
It depends on which path you want to take.
The path that leads to the truth
or the opposite.
Why did you quit your job at the school?
Was that because of Yeon-jin as well?
Not entirely.
I'd never be able to become
a good teacher anyway.
This is the address you asked for.
Only one family member lives there.
It's her mother.
And the name of the deceased
is Yoon So-hee.
It's my understanding…
that she's still in a mortuary.
Which hospital is it?
Do you intend to move her?
Or
are you trying to help?
Seoul Joo General Hospital.
Here.
It's what you asked me
to dig into the other day.
The details are inside.
JOO YEO-JEONG
By the way, his family owns
Seoul Joo General Hospital.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
10TH ANNIVERSARY,
FAMILY OF DOCTORS BECOME PARTNERS
Why did you protect Ye-sol?
Using her would have been
the fastest way to torment Yeon-jin.
If I had, it would have pained you too.
Once this revenge is over, will you…
find happiness?
I hope so.
I wish to be happy enough…
that I could die.
I want to be happy, just by that much.
What a rude motherfucker.
HA DO YEO NG
LET'S MEET UP
I said, let's meet. It's important.
You got Hye-jeong's call, right?
Son Myeong-o.
I heard he died.
You must know since you live together.
I heard.
I figured you'd be the first to know
apart from his family.
He worked here, after all.
What did the police say?
Did you hear anything
about the cause of death or whatever?
I did.
They told me where Son Myeong-o was found.
Where was he found?
That abandoned building
where So-hee fell.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry, Yeon-jin.
I threw away those clothes. I really did.
Fine.
Really?
Thank you so much, Yeon-jin.
That's a given. What else?
I'll stay out of your sight and…
That's also a given. What else?
I knew it. You're not really sorry.
That's not it.
I'm really sorry, Yeon-jin. I really am.
Is that right?
Then strip. It's not too late.
But here's the thing.
I recently bought
a really expensive ASMR file.
You're the one
who saw him last, aren't you?
At Siesta.
That bastard actually
recorded me that day?
Oh, that must be it.
That's what Hye-jeong has on me.
So, what's in it?
Something shocking.
Fuck, Yeon-jin!
So, what are you going to do?
I'm Ye-sol's mother.
I'm the mother of your daughter.
You know it all now. What will you do?
You have to save me.
You have to save me and Ye-sol.
You're our only hope now, Jae-jun.
Give it to me straight.
What did you do to Myeong-o?
It was an accident.
I took care of it.
I don't understand how it got to this.
This was definitely Moon Dong-eun's doing.
A doctor is helping her.
His family owns Seoul Joo Hospital!
And that's where her body is!
Joo Hospital?
I'm in such a mess right now.
I'll bring Ye-sol with me.
I'll bring her and come to you, okay?
We can't let her become
a murderer's daughter, can we?
So…
I was with you that day.
Right?
I see.
We must have been very naughty
that day too.
Right?
Ji-hyeon.
-Where's Ye-sol?
-Well…
Your friend's here.
Wow, your drawing is so good, Ye-sol.
Do you want to work as my apprentice?
Do you like to get high, Ye-sol?
Come with me.
Oh! What's with the fuss?
I meant "get hired."
Ye-sol, let's make that a promise, okay?
Bye!
You psychotic bitch!
Wow, fuck.
You almost seemed like a good mother.
You must have spent a fortune on lawyers.
You're out already?
See? I knew it was you, bitch.
I'm just looking out for you.
You should be more careful.
-You're not a first offender anymore.
-See?
I knew it was you.
The asshole who wrote about my exhibition.
It's the same guy who sucked up to you.
Reporter Kang Hyeong-jin of Doowon Daily.
What the hell are you saying?
You're being ridiculous.
Don't you think it's ridiculous
that a citizen on drugs got streamed live
on the day you got exposed?
You exposed me so you can bury your news.
You blabbed about the tax evasion,
didn't you?
Thanks for letting me know.
I seem to have just lost two friends.
I'm telling the truth. It was here.
Why would I come here just to lie to you?
Save it!
You're going to handle it, right?
Hey.
What are you looking at? Fuck, what is it?
What are you looking at?
I'm not going down by myself,
you fucking bitch!
NEW MESSAGE
DONG! EUN!
Where are you?
I came to see you. Where are you?
Far away.
How far away are you?
Want a ride?
You got the wrong person.
I have a crush on someone else.
I still have two kilometers left to run.
We said hello, so you can go on.
I'll run home.
Do you jog like this often?
You take good care of your body.
I said, I have a crush on someone else.
Is it because you're a doctor?
Stamina is what determines the winner.
Who are you up against?
I said, you got the wrong guy.
I really have a crush on someone else.
She's very pretty.
I'll leave if you don't hop in.
I know you're not going to leave.
You say you will, but…
Hey, Dong-eun?
Wait up!
Plate number 4225! Moon Dong-eun!
God.
That came out of nowhere.
Why are you hugging me?
Because I missed you.
We just saw each other.
But that was so long ago.
What's the use of me being on guard
if you run at me like this?
Why are you on guard around me?
Because you're a kindhearted lunatic.
Oh, right.
Your landlord at Eden Apartments.
Did you know her before?
-Did I know her?
-Yeah.
She said you saved her life.
I don't think so.
I never had the time to save anyone,
nor did I lead a life of virtue.
Well, I can see that.
It's strange, isn't it?
-I take back the "kindhearted" part.
-Jeez, you're so strict.
See you later, then.
I still have a kilometer left.
You're saying,
a missing person turned up dead and--
Is it a yes or a no?
Will they do an autopsy or not?
Without proof of suicide or accident,
an autopsy is a must.
Even if the family says no?
Even if three generations oppose it?
Even if.
If the police suspect foul play,
they can force the autopsy with a warrant.
Then there's no doubt they'll do it.
So I can't stop this.
You're scaring me.
You used to ask about tax evasion.
Why the new interest in criminal law?
Okay, I'm cutting off the mother.
Bye. I have a meeting.
Hey, where are you going?
Why are you cutting your mother off?
Sit down, it's a long story.
Want a sip?
I'd prefer it if you'd get to the point.
You'd rather get the beating
over with, huh?
I guess you never got beaten before.
Well, I can relate.
It was my first beating the other day too.
So I didn't know how to fight back.
I said,
get to the point.
I almost cussed when you interrupted me.
Suit yourself, then.
You already know
that this place is special
to Yeon-jin, don't you?
Don't cross the line.
October 19th.
It's a recording on Son Myeong-o's phone.
Take it and give it a listen.
You know who Son Myeong-o is.
You used to look for him too.
That prick was last spotted here,
and the last person
to see him was Yeon-jin.
That's what I meant earlier.
Right. Here's something more important.
I only cottoned on to this today,
but there used to be
an expensive bottle of liquor
that had a good grip to it.
But I see now that the bottle is missing.
Do you mind asking Yeon-jin where it is?
Please say to her,
"What an expensive murder, Yeon-jin."
-So you're saying--
-Yes, exactly.
Yeon-jin's a murderer.
Cut the crap.
What do you want, then?
For me to report her?
Wow, you're nuts.
If I wanted that,
I would've done it myself.
I want you to be my accomplice.
I won't hand this over to the police.
Divorce her
and give up your parental rights.
That's all I need.
We don't want the kid's mother
to become a murderer, do we?
Be it Jeon Ye-sol or Ha Ye-sol.
Are you…
using Ye-sol to threaten me?
A long time ago…
I gave Yeon-jin an alibi.
Apparently, a girl she was with
on a rooftop had died.
But guess what?
Someone she was with
on October 19th died, again.
What should we do now?
Are you going to do it this time?
Give Yeon-jin her alibi?
Honey!
What on earth is going on?
Get in. You must hurry.
Go to Ji-min's. I'll be right there.
Call me when you arrive.
HONG YEONG-AE
-Yeah.
-Let's meet up today.
After all, we go back 40 years.
We should at least end things in person.
What time?
PARK YEON-JIN
Hello?
I'm working for the lady
from Pyeongchang-dong.
I'm texting you the address.
See you there.
I can't believe this is happening!
Dinner's almost ready.
I'm just waiting for this to boil.
God, shut up about cheonggukjang!
Aren't you sick of it?
You can have the goddamn stuff
by yourself!
Oh, and…
I might be away for a few days.
Don't even think about calling me, okay?
Where are you? Across the street?
Walk up that way a bit
and cross the street.
-The bag is heavy, so please hurry!
-Up?
Yeah, okay. I'll be there in a second!
Where are we going?
You should at least tell me.
We're here.
Where are we?
Things used to be simple with you.
You only worked for money.
But I guess I'm the end of all that.
What are you on about?
You only get probation
for manslaughter, right?
And the odds are in your favor
if there's an eyewitness.
Are you out of your mind?
Shit!
Is he dead?
He's dead, right?
Fuck!
Hey, this asshole is…
Did you--
There's been an accident.
I hit a jaywalker. Please hurry!
Fuck.
Are you mad?
You shouldn't have called it in.
I wasn't drunk.
I was driving under the speed limit.
I couldn't see properly
because of the rain.
Handle it. You're an eyewitness now.
What?
You think I'm a bloody idiot, don't you?
Did you think I wouldn't find out
that you two were a team?
What the hell are you talking about?
We're not a team!
How else would he have known?
Only you know what happened back then.
How in the world would I know?
It wasn't me!
Were you always this fucking crazy?
Don't bullshit me.
You're not getting out of this.
Whether you're in it or not,
you have to handle this.
I haven't destroyed the evidence
that proves we're accomplices.
Yeon-jin's name tag.
God damn it!
You've fucking lost your marbles.
That evidence works against you
more than me, Yeong-ae.
It proves your kid's a murderer!
I'm an ordinary housewife.
How would I be in possession of evidence
that was handed to the cops?
It's still sealed in the way you gave me.
The informant, the dead kid,
Yeon-jin, me, or you!
I bet the evidence has the DNA
of at least one of us.
What a joke!
Fuck!
What the hell are you doing,
you crazy bitch?
I'm just trying to get the best out of you
before you run away. So what?
I'm bringing you down with me
no matter what.
So take care of this.
We're in this together,
so we either live or die together,
Yeong-jun.
Light the candles in the shrine
and bleed a chicken.
I will.
But did you come with her?
Huh?
Oh, you startled me.
We're not open today,
not at this hour anyway.
Off you go.
So, you're only working
your side job today?
You set out very quickly.
Maybe because Yeon-jin's mom was involved?
Vroom, wham!
Who are you?
Wow.
We meet again at such an unexpected place.
Why didn't you turn on the lights?
What brings you here, Mr. Joo?
I find that stranger.
Oh, so you came here
without any prior knowledge.
Twice, at that.
I'm the owner here, you see.
No way.
I was looking for a bathroom…
I'm so startled,
I can't think of a better excuse.
OUT OF BUSINESS
DO NOT ENTER
Open the gate!
I'm trying to keep trespassers out.
Take today, for example.
You're doing this on purpose.
What did you do to me the other day?
What did you do to me
when you put me under that day?
The procedure?
Your jawline looks slim now,
making you look beautiful.
I don't know what that bitch said to you,
but don't meddle
when you don't know the whole story.
You know
I practice dermatology too, right?
I can tell by looking at a scar
what kind of pain
the abuser tried to inflict.
It was the work of the devil.
You were looking for something.
This is it, right?
Take it.
I've already got what I need.
You can open the gate yourself.
The chains are a trick. It's not locked.
And I won't charge you for parking.
I have a feeling
that's your last lucky break.
Drive safe.
On days like this,
there are a lot of jaywalking accidents.
NEW MESSAGE
MOM
I'm at the police station. Pick me up.
The rain was pouring.
And the man jumped out of nowhere.
We tested for DUI at the site,
so we know she was sober.
He was jaywalking.
There was no negligence on her part.
She has no record.
She didn't flee the scene.
That's all there is.
Yes, sir. I'm well aware of what happened.
But there were no cameras at the site.
We're trying to get in touch
with the family,
so please stay put for a minute, ma'am.
As for you, you can go home, Chief.
Okay, good work.
Don't worry too much.
It's important to come to an agreement
with the bereaved. Keep that in mind.
I will.
Thanks, Shin.
Right. I'll keep in touch.
Bye.
Have a safe trip, sir.
It was raining,
and I couldn't see.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry!
You don't have to say sorry to me, ma'am.
-No, I'm so sorry!
-Please try to calm down.
Mr. Son Myeong-o was found dead.
Did you hear?
No. Where was he found?
You don't seem that surprised.
Did you talk to Park Yeon-jin?
Or am I a suspect right now?
We checked Mr. Son's emails.
He was looking into the Yoon So-hee case.
And the person
who gave him the information
was you, Ms. Moon.
Is that illegal?
There are many people
who are far worse than me.
How disappointing.
What exactly is going on?
What exactly happened between you all?
I already told you everything.
Although you didn't believe me.
That was all true?
WINTER OF 2004
Do you smoke, by any chance?
The list of evidence shows
that a lighter was found
at the site where So-hee died.
When you flick a lighter, don't you leave
some sort of DNA trace?
Mom!
Did you bring your car?
Let's go to the shaman.
Why would we go there right now?
What's going on?
I feel safer there.
It's better than going to a psychiatrist.
Do you have the family's phone number?
Don't worry about that.
I'll take care of everything.
How can I not worry?
You said someone died!
This is exactly what the reporters want.
Yeon-jin.
I told you this before.
Everyone makes mistakes.
But you never find a solution in the past.
It's always in front of you.
Someone died. That was yesterday.
Today, we'll do what we need to do.
What are you saying?
If that man has the original file,
you should make a decision soon.
If he leaks it first,
it will be very bad for us.
Find a town in the UK or Ireland
where Ye-sol could go.
A guardian will accompany her.
It's snowing heavily.
Be careful.
Yes, sir. You too.
KIM JIN-HUN
WE HAVE A DATE FOR YOUR INTERVIEW
Where's the shaman?
She's preparing for a special ritual
that is coming up.
Hello?
I'm not sure if I should tell you this.
It's about Kang Hyeon-nam's husband.
That bastard died yesterday.
He got hit by a car while jaywalking.
Is this your husband?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
That is
my husband.
Yeon-jin!
It's been a while. How have you been?
Yeon-jin. It's me, So-hee.
The girl that moved schools.
Do you remember me?
What are you doing right now?
Should I strip out of these clothes?
Do you want me to take these clothes off
and give them to you?
What is this?
What's this bullshit?
Then strip. It's not too late.
Yeon-jin, please.
These aren't even the same clothes.
I don't care what you're wearing.
Why do the likes of you not listen
when I ask nicely?
Are you wearing a sweater or lint?
One minute.
My patience...
I said, strip.
That's enough.
I'm not scared of you anymore.
You're nothing by yourself.
What the fuck are you saying?
Did you watch a teen movie?
I was only scared of your money.
I pity you, actually.
So I'm going to forgive you.
Because I'm a better person than you are.
Wow.
You just made me a pitiful bitch
who is worse than you are.
Fuck, that's a lot to take in at once.
Is that right?
Then can you allow this pitiful bitch
to remove the lint on your sweater?
You said you're the better person.
So you should dress properly.
What are you doing?
If you move,
I'll go to your school tomorrow.
Go on. Try running your mouth now.
Help!
Go away!
SCHOOL WITHDRAWAL FORM
Mom.
Mom, what do I do?
What do I do, Mom?
Seriously, what am I going to do with you?
-Why did you skip your lessons again?
-Mom!
I think I messed up!
We were just fooling around on the roof,
and she got caught on fire.
The girl who moved schools.
She was struggling by herself,
and then she fell.
It's true!
It was just the two of us!
Mom.
Mom, what do I do? Huh?
Hello?
Hello? Mom?
Get a grip, Yeon-jin!
First, get away from there.
Mr. Shin will be calling you soon.
Stop crying and talk properly!
Any witnesses? Did anyone see you?
No.
-I don't think so.
-Make sure! Look around you.
There is no one. I'm sure!
EVIDENCE
They didn't do a DNA test at the time.
The report says
the lighter was used by the deceased…
Where are you going?
Forensics. Wrap it up here.
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon